if we talk about the Indian markets the
Indian markets witness a sharp
Connection in the week on Y and somehow
trying to manage to hold the 18 000
devils
however we are seeing some stock
specific action in the sector rotation
into the market as of now and expecting
a long build up into the insurance
sector as of now so in this video I have
got a buy recommendation from the
insurance insurance space the stock name
is icsa Lombard the stock is listed with
the name of ICC General Insurance that
is ICICI GI
if you talk about the technical
parameters of Issa General Insurance in
the recent past stock has formed the
double bottom pattern onto the technical
charts around 1115 levels and since
they're on the stock has witnessed a
sharp recovery uh to once and cash the
momentum above its 200 is exponential
exploration under the daily charts since
then the stock is went into the phase of
long consolidation from past four to
five weeks and last week the stock has
given a fresh breakout up after the
prolonged consolidation phase
so we are expecting the further upside
momentum into the stock till 1360 to
1380 levels so we we recommend to go
long in icsa general insurance from the
current levels you need to keep a
trading stop loss below 1200 and 1200
levels for the Target potential of 1380
levels we are recommending this script
with a Time Horizon of say five to seven
weeks as a disclaimer I want to add that
I do not have any financial interest
into the given script but our clients
could or may have any position thank you